superdry.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy - Superdry

### privacy policy

Superdry takes your privacy very seriously and treats all your personal information as confidential. This privacy policy sets out how we treat your personal information and what we use it for. This policy applies whether you contact us through our website or through a store, promotion or any other channel.

### information about us

Superdry is the trading name of the Superdry plc group of companies. Superdry plc or SuperGroup Internet Ltd is the data controller responsible for protecting personal information you provide to us. Both are an English companies, whose address is Unit 60, The Runnings, Cheltenham, Gloucestershire GL51 9NW, United Kingdom.

### information collected

Website: When you place an order or set up an account through one of our Superdry websites, SuperGroup Internet Ltd will collect your name, billing address, delivery address, contact details (including email and telephone numbers), gender and password. We will also keep details of all of your orders. We will collect information about your use of our website. We do not hold your payment card details. Financial transactions take place directly and securely with our payment provider.

E-receipts: If you sign up to receive e-receipts in a Superdry store, Superdry plc will collect your name, email address, home address, date of birth and gender. If you are an existing website customer, we will link this information through to your information held by SuperGroup Internet Ltd above so that you have one customer profile with us.

Competitions, promotions: If you enter a competition or promotion we are running, Superdry plc may ask you to provide your name, email address, home address and gender.

Customer services: If you contact our customer services representatives, Superdry plc will ask you to provide your name, email address and home address, and the reasons for contacting us.

Opting into direct marketing: When you contact us through any of these channels, we will ask you whether you want to opt into receiving our newsletter and other marketing communications from us. If you decide to opt in, SuperGroup Internet Ltd will record this opt in on your customer profile.

### what we use your information for

Web: When you place an order or set up an account through one of our Superdry websites, we will use your personal data to:

  * process your orders, communicate with you about your orders, and deliver your products; 
  * update our records and maintain your account with us; 
  * prevent or detect fraud; 
  * ask for feedback on our products, website and services; 
  * conduct market research; 
  * monitor your browsing history within our website so that we can (i) provide you with information and suggestions to help you to improve your browsing experience; and (ii) improve our website and any services we offer to you or the public.

E-receipts: If you sign up to receive e-receipts in a Superdry store, we will use your personal data to send you an electronic receipt for the products you purchase in-store.

Competitions, promotions: If you enter a competition or promotion, we will use your personal data to administer the competition or promotion.

Customer services: If you contact our customer services representatives, we will use your personal data to investigate and resolve your query.

Direct marketing: If you have opted in to receive marketing communications from us, we will use your personal data to notify you of Superdry products, promotions, competitions and special offers that may be of interest to you. These notifications will be sent to you online (either by email as a newsletter, or by social media or search engine as banners or adverts).

### How Long We Keep Your Information For

We will keep your information for the following periods of time:

Web: If you set up an account through one of our Superdry websites, we will retain your personal data within the website for three years after your last order. If you use a guest check out without setting up an account, we will retain your personal data within the website database for 90 days. Data relating to each of your orders will be kept for seven years.

E-receipts: If you sign up to receive e-receipts in a Superdry store, we will retain your personal data for seven years.

Competitions, promotions: If you enter a competition or promotion, we will delete your personal data as soon as we have completed the competition or promotion.

Customer services: If you contact our customer services representatives, we retain your personal data for seven years.

### How To Opt Out

If you have opted in to receiving marketing communications from us, you can opt out at any time by:

  * emailing us at [care@superdry.com](mailto:care@superdry.com) with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line; 
  * clicking on "unsubscribe" on any marketing email you receive from us; or 
  * logging into "My Account" on the website and editing your account details.

Please allow up to 5 days for unsubscribe requests to be processed.

For guidance on how to turn off cookies, see section 8. Cookies below.

### disclosure of your information

We may share your personal data with any company within the Superdry plc group of companies for the purposes listed in this policy.

We will not disclose your personal information to any third party except as follows:

  * If you have opted in to receiving marketing communications, we may share your information our third party service providers who provide email distribution services or with social media companies providing digital marketing services. 
  * We will provide your personal data to our business partners who provide, ordering, logistics, fulfilment, and other services in order to process your orders, deliver your products, and provide customer care. 
  * We may provide your personal data to agencies undertaking market research and analysis on our behalf. They may contact you by email or telephone to ask you for your feedback and comments on our products, website and services.

All of these disclosures would be made under contractual arrangements to ensure confidentiality, and carried out in accordance with the requirements of the relevant Data Protection regulations.

We may also use aggregated information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the website and our services. We may provide such aggregated information to third parties, but these statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual.

### cookies

A cookie is a small piece of information sent to your computer, mobile or other device when you visit a website. Cookies are sent by a web server to a web browser, to enable the server to collect information from the browser and recognise your device on future visits.

When you first visit our website you will be asked if you accept our cookies. We use cookies to keep track of your current shopping session, to personalise your experience, to store items in your shopping bag, and trying to ensure that the adverts or offers you see online are more relevant to you.

  * If you click to accept cookies, you are opting-in to SuperGroup Internet Ltd using your personal information for these purposes. 
  * If you do not accept our cookies, the functionality of our website will be severely limited.

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this, look at the help menu on your browser. However, if you do not accept cookies your user experience on our website may be affected and you will be unable to purchase products from our website.

Cookies can be divided into four types:

Category 1: Strictly Necessary Cookies

These cookies are essential for the website to provide services you have asked for such as remembering your shopping bag items.

Category 2: Performance Cookies

This type collect anonymous information on how people use our website and the data is merged with other users to enable us to improve how the website operates. For example, we utilise Google Analytics cookies to help us understand how customers arrive at our website, browse or use our website and highlight areas where we can improve areas such as navigation, shopping experience and marketing campaigns. The data stored by these cookies never shows personal details from which your individual identity can be established, but our third party providers (such as Google) may associate this data with personal data they already hold about you.

Category 3: Functionality Cookies 

These remember choices you make such as language, search parameters such as size, colour or product line. These can then be used to provide you with an experience more appropriate with your selections and make the visits more tailored and pleasant. The information is also merged with other users on an anonymous basis to enable us to improve how the website operates. For example our Saved Items feature utilises a cookie to remember the products which you have expressed a wish to save whilst browsing our website.

Category 4: Targeting Cookies or Advertising Cookies

These cookies collect information about your browsing habits in order to make advertising relevant to you and your interests. They remember the websites you have visited and that information is shared with other parties such as advertisers. For example we use third party companies such as Criteo to provide you with more personalised adverts when visiting other websites.

### protecting your information

Our website uses up-to-date industry procedures to protect your personal information. We also protect the security of your data during transmission using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption software.

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you.

### access, correcting and deleting your information

If you would like to access information we hold about you, or would like us to correct or delete your information please contact us at [care@superdry.com](mailto:care@superdry.com) If you ask us to delete information, please be aware that we are entitled to keep a record of our transactions with you for legal and audit purposes, which we will retain for the period set out in section 5. How Long We Keep Your Information For.
